Would I go on the Joe Buddton podcast?
Um,
I don't want I just don't want to go
places no more where people have said
things mean about me. Like, I wouldn't
have gone on Tasha Kay if I had actually
done the research that I should have
done and seen the way that she's talked
about me in the past. She was lovely in
person. I'm not going to take that from
her. But the way that she has spoken
about me in the past is deplorable.
Deplorable.
Like truly truly deplorable. So, like I,
you know, there's people on that podcast
that I consider my friends,
right? You know, I've known Joe since I
was 19, but then he has other people on
there that I'm just not interested in
talking about or talking to and and they
have had my name in their mouth and I
just feel like they are not of any would
I go on the joke to me. So, that's my
answer to that. But like Dr. Mark Lamont
Hill and Don't Call Me White Girl. Like,
those are my friends. I will watch
Dave's comedy, but I'm not going to give
you feedback on it. I'm also a sensitive
person. I'm a sensitive gal. So, it's
like I don't like when people that don't
know me have [ __ ] to say about me, and I
don't like when people that do know me
have [ __ ] to say about me.
So, IT'S LIKE, DON'T TALK ABOUT ME
unless it's positive. That's how I feel
because a lot of times people can't seem
to just talk about the thing I'm talking
about. They have to talk about like me
as a what what they consider me as a
person and it's like you don't even know
me as a person to me.
>> I am Savvy Mike in this is I am Savvy
Mike TV and well I don't blame Amanda
Sills for not wanting to go on that
boring podcast anymore. You know Joe's
on the ompic. His name is now Joe
Zimpic.
You know just just a bunch of you know
at the end of the day I still [ __ ] with
Ish. I don't think she like ish, but I
like Ish. I don't really like Mona, but
she likes Mona. I don't mind Amanda
Sills. [laughter]
This whatnot. Just know definitely don't
[ __ ] with your butt. But outside of all
of that, I don't mind Amanda Sills. And
I guess she has some beef with everybody
up there outside of Mona and and Mark
Lamont Hill. I guess everything else
everybody had to say, including Joe
Button in that clearly. But she says
she's known Joe since she was 19. So,
who knows? But yeah, I mean, I like
Amanda SS. And we're going to get into
another clip from her because she has
some things to say about the the
Venezuela stuff and I I I didn't watch
it and I would like to react to it here
cuz that's what we do over here and I am
Savvy Mike TV. We react to things that I
haven't watched that I have some
interest in and hopefully you sit and
watch with me. So, either way, that was
that. Let's let's get into everything
else because if you don't know, Trump is
taking over Venezuela. He's running it
now from everything you heard from what
I know. It's for the oil.
But everything else everybody is else is
saying is is naroterrorism, all this
extra [ __ ] But it's really for the oil
and Amanda Sils has some things to say
about it. Let's listen.
>> There is no such thing as international
law. International law is essentially
the same as the Constitution. It was put
on record to protect a particular
people. However, since then, it does
whatever it wants to do. Those people do
whatever they want to do. And all you're
essentially doing is constantly holding
them holding up to them like, "No, look
what you said." Which is what black
people have been doing for, you know,
time and time again. So, every time I
see folks talk about this is a violation
of international law, I'm just like, the
people who made up international law did
not make it up for international
purposes. They made it up for
themselves. This is why I get so annoyed
when I see Professor Jeffrey Sachs, who
I know is a very smart, principal man,
continuously talk about the United
Nations as if it was formed for any
other reason than colonial control.
Stop. I don't like that because it is
absolutely disingenuous to the realities
and it actually is a blind spot of
racism when you say that because it
assumes that the United States was at
any point ever about anything other than
colonialism and imperialism. The men who
started the United States were literally
making money off of colonialism. So to
there was never any point where it
wasn't a part of that system.
Furthermore, when you talk about the
founding of the United Nations, the
United Nations was founded after World
War II for the purpose of not stopping
the world from going to war again. The
United Nations was founded for the
purpose of the United States
controlling, sorry, the United Nations
was founded so the United States could
control the rest of the world. And the
United States is not being controlled by
Americans. That's another conversation
for another time. It's just a tool. It's
just a tool to say that there's
international law means that there would
have to be an enforcing there would have
to be an enforcing body. There is not an
enforcing body. And for what it's worth,
to actually consider the United Nations
to be anything legitimate makes no sense
when you know that there are literal
people there are countries in the United
Nations who have veto power over the
rest of the United Nations. It is not a
majority rules body. Correct, Moses?
Right now, I'm sewing my sweatpants
because somehow I ripped a hole in them
because I was sitting on the floor and
then there was like a nail and I ripped
the nail. So, I also think there's an
evil eye on me, but I'll deal with that
later today. But I'm sewing the pants
because normally in the past I would
have just like been like, "Oh, well
that's that." And gotten rid of them.
But in my effort to curb my consumerism
and be much more responsible about
keeping things, I am sewing them. Of
course, THERE'S CORRUPTION. THE UNITED
NATIONS IS CORRUPT. OKAY. SO, let's do
some critical thinking. So, if you let
let's take it out of the United Nations.
Let's put it in a different context. If
you're on a team, right, and
only one person on that team gets to
determine the plays that you run, is
everyone equal on that team? Now,
everybody brings a different skill to
the team.
>> No, they're called the coach, Amanda.
That's what That's what the coach does.
The coach calls every play. He might
give the quarterback some leeway
sometimes, but I mean, depending on what
type of team, are you talking about a
football team, even a basketball team?
Unless you're LeBron James, the coaches
is usually the one calling the plays.
>> But is is everybody on that team equal?
No, they're not. So on certain like
sports teams for instance, you know that
like Steph is GOING TO TAKE THE SHOT.
STEPH IS GOING TO TAKE THE SHOT. Not
everybody has green light power. Not
everybody has green light power but
Steph has green light power. You have to
know that the United Nations everybody
does not have green light power. And
more importantly everybody only
everybody doesn't have red light power.
So the United States can stop the entire
governing body of the United Nations
from passing a resolution. However,
there hold on, let me block this person.
However, [clears throat]
when the United Nations wants to do
something,
it doesn't require
the entire body of the United Nations to
do it. So you have to be able to look at
those types of dynamics to determine the
efficacy of a body. You can't you have
to acknowledge that when a governing
body comes together and the determinance
on who gets to stop or who gets to
continue things is is limited. You have
to ask yourself why is it limited? Thank
you face. Thank you face guard Kennedy.
let them know the block hand is quick.
But again, and this is where so many
people are missing it. You're thinking
of the United States as if it is some
like individual entity just out here
acting up, you know, just just some
rogue state doing what it want to do.
And it's not. It is funded. It is
funded. You have to understand it is
funded. Which is why the only way that's
ever going to change the world is if we
figure out a way to move outside of
funds. Good luck with capitalism. Good
luck living in a capitalistic world, let
alone country. But yeah, good good luck
with that one. Manda Sills. But you
know, regardless of it, I feel like this
this United Nations conversation was was
going on and happening because right
now, if you look at the news, they're
they're saying that the United States or
or Trump in general needed the United
Nations approval for and he he did it
without their approval. And you know,
the US would argue, well, buddy, the
president of Venezuela was a criminal
and he needed to face justice because we
had all these charges that we needed to
bring against him. And while I guess
that's a good argument, I I don't know
what more the UN can do outside of that
other than kind of wave their finger and
go, "You're wrong for not getting our
approval." I don't know. We shall see.
But I think that's where this the the
the foundation of this conversation
started cuz she really didn't even talk
about Venezuela. I'm sorry guys.
Hopefully I didn't waste the Amanda
Sills fans times. They got some content
and hopefully you know I didn't waste
yours. Even if you're not an Amanda
Sills fan, let me know what you think in
the comments below. As always, I am
Savvy Mike and this is I am Savvy Mike
TV where we don't waste your time.
Peace.